royallifeservices.com 2018-09-01

# Buy TV, Mobile, Fashion Online Shopping :: Friends Mart

#### Pricacy Policy

Shadow The aim of this privacy policy is to aware you regarding the parameters set by the company for your information that you provide to Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd. ("Royal Life") through the website www.royallifemart.com ("Website") or in any other form. We offer our pledge to protect and secure the private information you enter on our website when you use our website. This statement describes you know what information we collect when you use our products and services, why we collect it and how we use it to stay in touch with you. Royal Life reserves the right to amend the policy from time to time. In this privacy statement ("Statement"), the terms:- "We", "our" and "us" are referred to Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd. ("Royal Life") and other entities owned by Royal Life. "You" and "your" are referred to RBO’s Distributor, Customers, visitors, users, and others who use this website. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

We are constantly improving the Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd website and the tools you can use to manage the data that you provide to us. Please refer to this page from time to time to see any new policies about the use of these new features.   
You shall provide complete, true, accurate and current information. All the information you provide us will be kept in secure and inviolable storage. We may also collect information about those you know such as your upline, your guest, and your belongings. Royal Life may collect your information through the website at several points as follows: Registration; Bank Details Storage; Surveys and promotions 

### Our Commitment

This Statement sets out the Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd privacy policy in respect of personal information which you may provide to Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd. Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd recognises that your privacy is very important to you and we are committed to promoting confidence in the manner in which your personal information is handled by us. The statement that follows explains how Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd collects, uses, discloses and protects this information on its website. 

### REGISTRATION

For the purpose of becoming Authorized Distributor of Royal Life you need to provide your personal information such as name, age, date of birth, address, contact details, e-mail address, gender and occupation. 

### Supporting Industry Best Practice

Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd is bound by, and committed to supporting, the National Privacy Principles (NPPs) set out in the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000. The aim of Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd is both to support and to ensure that it complies with the NPPs that form the basis of laws introduced to strengthen privacy protection for the general public. We believe that in supporting industry best practice this statement will address any potential concerns you may have about how personal information you provide to us is stored, used and accessed. 

### Collection of Information

Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd receives and stores transaction information, information you enter on our website or have provided to us in application, registration or administration processes.   
Wherever it is lawful and practicable, Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd will endeavour to provide you with the option of not identifying yourself or not providing personal information when entering transactions with us. However, failure to provide the full and complete information we request may result in a limited ability on our part to offer or deliver complete services to you.   
No personal information is collected when you browse anonymously. Anonymous browsing is when personally identifiable information is not required by an individual to gain access to our web site. In addition, personally identifiable information such as name, birth date and contact details (email addresses) are only collected when you make an enquiry, place an order, book on a course or register to use the member only section. All other information will be requested from you directly.   
Information collected is kept for as long as it is needed to service your account and provide services and products requested by you. When your information is no longer needed for these purposes we will destroy or permanently render anonymous any information held about you. 

### Use and Disclosure of Information

The primary purpose in collecting information from you is to enable us to fulfil our business commitments to you in providing management education and training, consultancy, events, membership and to improve these services to you and other clients of Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd. We may use the information you provide to help improve the services we deliver to you, measure consumer interest in Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd services, inform you of other Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd products and services or to comply with requirements under the law.   
We will only collect and store information about you that is necessary. The information you provide may be used to offer, provide and improve our services to you and may also be disclosed to other parties such as Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd, organisations contracted to operate and maintain Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd databases, provide IT support Services and distribute Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd information, and other services providers that are affiliated with or support the provision of educational services offered by Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd.   
Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd does not permit these parties to use information about you for any other purpose than to perform the services that Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd has instructed them to provide. All suppliers, agents and third party companies must sign a confidentiality agreement with Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd before any personal information is disclosed by Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd.   
Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd will not, without your consent, disclose personal information for any purpose (a Secondary purpose) other than for the main purpose (Primary purpose) of fulfilling our business commitments to you, except where:   
it is required or authorised by law or for purposes of law enforcement and matters directly related to law enforcement or the prevention of unlawful activity; the Secondary Purpose is related to the primary purpose (or directly related when sensitive information is involved) and there is a reasonable expectation that we would use or disclose the information in the circumstances; Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd reasonably believes it is necessary to prevent any serious and imminent threat to any person’s life, health or safety or the public’s health or safety. Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd will not otherwise disclose your personal information to any other party without your consent. 

### Third Party Relationships

To provide you with a more informative online experience Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd does use the online resources, from time to time, of suppliers, agents and business partners. Such services comprise of links to third party sites that promote additional services and products. In any such relationship Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd takes all reasonable steps to ensure that these parties have and enforce an adequate privacy policy. Understandably, the privacy policy of a third party might be different to that of Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd and it is advisable that you carefully review any third party’s privacy policy before using the site’s products and/or services.   
Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd uses Web Advantage to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card transactions over the Internet. Confidential information including client credit card details are encrypted the moment they are transmitted from the client’s browser to the banking network using industry standard SSL 128-bit RC4 encryption technology.   
A client’s credit card details are not stored anywhere on the Internet and the only company who has access to this data is the merchant’s bank. The bank also sends confirmation information via the same encryption technology back to the client’s browser. These secure processes provide clients with peace of mind when purchasing online. 

### Storage and Security of Personal Information

Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd will use all reasonable endeavours to ensure that you only provide personal information in a secure environment and when the information is no, longer needed it will be destroyed or permanently render anonymous.   
Where indicated by a lock (on the browser window), we protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information, you input. In conjunction with our key suppliers and agents, we operate secure data networks protected by an industry standard firewall and password protection system. We also take care to ensure that we have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, unauthorised access, alteration, modification or disclosure of your user data under our control.   
The security of any information (including personal information) downloaded and stored on your PC/Server etc is the responsibility of the individual. The individual is also responsible for the correct configuration of the hardware and software he/she uses to access an Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd website, along with the physical security and maintenance of that equipment.   
Notwithstanding the fact that we take all reasonable steps to protect your personal data including the use of encryption technology, we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose online. You can help us keep your personal information secure by ensuring that any password you use on our web site is kept strictly confidential, and by logging off when you have finished using a shared computer.   
Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd imposes strict rules on its employees who have access either to the databases that store your user information or to the servers that host our services and while we cannot guarantee that any unauthorised access, disclosure, loss, misuse or alteration to your data will not occur, we will take all reasonable steps to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. You accept the inherent security implications of dealing online over the Internet and will not hold Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd or its agents or suppliers responsible for any breach of security. 

### Cookies

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES A COOKIE STORE ?**  
For the most part a cookie will contain a string of text that contains information about the browser. To work, a cookie does not need to know where you are from; it only needs to remember your browser. Some Web sites do use cookies to store more personal information about you. However, this can be done only if you yourself have provided the Web site with that personal information. Legitimate Web sites will encrypt this personal information stored in the cookie to prevent unauthorized usage by another party with access to your cookie folder. Cookies have six parameters that can be passed to them: The name of the cookie. The value of the cookie. The expiration date of the cookie – this determines how long the cookie will remain active in your browser. The path the cookie is valid for – this sets the URL path the cookie us valid in. Web pages outside of that path cannot use the cookie. The domain the cookie is valid for. This makes the cookie accessible to pages on any of the servers when a site uses multiple servers in a domain. The need for a secure connection – this indicates that the cookie can only be used under a secure server condition, such as a site using SSL.   
Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd may use cookies to personalise and simplify your access to and use of our website. A cookie is a small data file that is downloaded from our website and stored in a text file on your hard drive. The information is made up of a string of letters and numbers which uniquely identifies your computer and any user name or password that you may have already registered on our web site. This information is used to authenticate or identify whether you are registered on our website, without requiring you to re-enter details each time you log on to our website. Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd Cookies cannot be used to obtain any other information on you or on your hard drive unless you have already provided such information. Cookies may also be used to “track” or “follow” your movement through our website. This will be used to determine which areas of our website are the most popular so that we can improve user’s access to relevant information on our services and make your online experience more informative and worthwhile. In particular, Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd Cookies may collect information such as the server your computer is logged onto, the browser type you are using, the time and date of your visit together with the particular pages you are accessing.   
If at any time you do not wish to accept Cookies or wish to delete existing Cookies, you may manually configure your browser to refuse Cookies or you may manually delete existing Cookies from your hard drive (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your Cookie preferences.) If you reject all Cookies, you will not be able to use areas of the Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd website that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, many areas within the Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd website do not require that you accept Cookies. 

### Trans-border Data Flows

Where, for the purpose of fulfilling our business commitments to you, we disclose personal information to persons involved in administering the services, our related entities or business partners (Permitted Persons), and such Permitted Persons are in a foreign country, Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd will not, without your consent, transfer personal information to such Permitted Persons unless:   
we reasonably believe that the Permitted Persons are subject to a law, binding scheme or contract or we have taken reasonable steps to ensure that the Permitted Persons are subject to a contract which effectively upholds principles for the fair handling of personal information that are substantially similar to the National Principles for the Fair Handling of Personal Information embodied in the Privacy Amendment Act 2000; or the transfer is necessary for: the performance of services requested by you; or for the purpose of fulfilling our business commitments to you; or to implement pre-contractual measures taken in response to a request by you; or the transfer is necessary for the conclusion or performance of a contract concluded in your interest, between Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd and a third party; or all of the following apply: the transfer is for your benefit; and it is impracticable to obtain your consent to the transfer; and if it were practicable you would be likely to consent to the transfer. Accessing and Changing Your Personal Information   
Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd attempts to ensure that all personal information collected and stored in its database systems is correct and accurate. You may at any time request access to the information we have collected from you and obtain a more in depth explanation about how the information is used by emailing us. We will endeavour to meet or advise of the outcome of a request within 15 business days of receipt.   
If at any time you wish to change personal information that is incorrect or wish to have your personal information deleted, please email us. Unless personal information is required for administrative or legal reasons we will take all reasonable steps to meet such requests at the earliest possible opportunity.   
You also have the right to request access to your personal information at any time. All our staff will be able to assist you with such a request and this information will be forwarded to you within 5 working days. 

### BANK DETAILS STORAGE

For the purpose of processing payments between you and Royal Life, you would require to provide your bank details as we make payment to you via account payee cheque or NEFT Bank transfer. It is our obligation to safeguard such information and we assure you that such information may not hold back on the website unless you choose to do so. 

### FEEDBACK AND COMPLAINTS

At any time you may provide us your feedback or any complaint for Royal Life product and services through this website mentioning your personal identifiable information so that we could cater you with more improved product and services. 

### USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

1) We may use your information to authenticate you whenever you want to login on our website to perform your task. You would need to enter a password to login you account.   
2) We may use your information for purpose of responding to your requests; monitoring and providing the Service; maintaining your ID account. 

### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

1) We assure you that we will not share, distribute, sell, trade, rent or otherwise by any such convey your personal information with third parties unless specified or required by law.   
2) We may share your information with your up line or any highest level distributor to provide you proper guidance and to deliver you a favourable experience. Your up line is obliged to not share or misuse your personal information, and also assure to apply the terms of the privacy policy while using your information.   
3) We may also share your information with third parties to send you updates about our products and services, to process your payments.   
4) While sharing your personal information with third parties we assure that your information is being used under contractual and technical protections. 

### BUSINESS TRANSFERS

We reserve the right to transfer any and all of your information that we collect from you to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Royal Life. 

### YOU CAN RETRIEVE AND UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION

At any time you can update or retrieve your submitted information on our website for marketing purposes, please contact us so that we may update your information in our records or you may go online to websites and update your own information. 

### AMENDMENTS

Royal Life reserves the right to amend, modify or revise any point described in this policy through a written notice on its website www.royallifemart.com. If you do not agree by such amendments, you may contact us within 15 days of such notification. Your continued relationship with Royal Life will be considered as an acceptance to all the amendments. 

### CONTACT US

For further queries or comments you have, you may contact us directly through our website or other email links you are provided through this website or in any other manner. We will try to reply you promptly. We use this information to respond to your questions and may record your comments to improve our customer service. 

### Liability Disclaimer

Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd will use all reasonable endeavours to protect and keep confidential any personally identifiable information in its possession in relation to its Members, subscribers or website visitors. If any confidential or personally identifiable information is accessed by a third party, whether by negligence or otherwise of Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd, its agents, suppliers, contractors, related bodies corporate, affiliates or associated parties, to the extent permitted by law, Royal Life Multi Trade Services Ltd is not liable for any loss, damage, costs, liability or other form of contribution.
